Sharwan Solanki

CS Undergrad.

I'm a 19-year-old Programmer / Developer / CS Undergrad currently living in Hyderabad. I've got a burning passion to want to help others with the code I create. I enjoy the limitless potential of impact that I can have on what I'm building. It's what pushes me to become a better developer every day. Other than coding, I love watching anime.

sharwansolanki01@gmail.com

Secunderabad, INDIA

in linkedin.com/in/NotSharwan

. 08801453981

sharwansolanki.ml

🕠 github.com/NotSharwan

EDUCATION

Computer Science and Engineering Institute of Aeronautical Engineering

08/2018 - Present 9.05 CGPA

Senior Secondary Education (Maths, Physics and Chemistry)

Narayana Junior College

07/2016 – 04/2018 98.6%

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Beta Tester Dark

02/2020 – Present Helping to improve the language.

Software Engineering Virtual Experience JPMorgan Chase & Co.

05/2020 - 05/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Added a chart to a trader's dashboard allowing them to better identify under/ over-valued stocks.
- Deployed an interface for relevant financial data feed and made the necessary adjustments to facilitate the monitoring of potential trade opportunities.
- Worked on JP Morgan Chase & Co. frameworks and tools.
- Displayed the data visually for traders (Trader's
 Dashboard) and used the Perspective (An interactive
 visualization component for large, real-time datasets)
 to work on the client-side web application so that it
 displays a graph that automatically updates as it gets
 data from the server application.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Website Design Project.

 Designed a personal web site using HTML,CSS,Javascript; viewable at www.sharwansolanki.ml

LANGUAGES

English

Telugu

Full Professional Proficiency

Hindi Full Professional Proficiency

Marwadi

ruttr

Professional Working Proficiency Native or Bilingual Proficiency

INTERESTS

Watching Anime

Playing Games

Codina

Reporter / Sub-EditorWorkplace/Company

09/2019 – Present

Compendium is the News and Publication Society of Institute Of Aeronautical Engineering